<display_items><item><name>mcp:MD_Metadata</name><displayName>Metadata (MCP)</displayName><description>root entity which defines metadata about a resource or resources</description></item><item><name>mcp:MD_DataIdentification</name><displayName>Data identification (MCP)</displayName><description>information required to identify an Australian Marine Community Profile dataset (Australian Marine Community Profile extension to ISO19115/19139)</description></item><item><name>mcp:currency</name><displayName>Temporal Currency</displayName><description>Describes the temporal currency of the resource (Australian Marine Community Profile extension to ISO19115/19139)</description></item><item><name>mcp:revisionDate</name><displayName>Revision Date</displayName><description>Date the metadata was last revised (Australian Marine Community Profile extension to ISO19115/19139)</description></item><item><name>mcp:samplingFrequency</name><displayName>Sampling Frequency</displayName><description>To describe the frequency of the sampled resource (Australian Marine Community Profile extension to ISO19115/19139)</description></item><item><name>mcp:temporalAggregation</name><displayName>Temporal Aggregation</displayName><description>Describes the temporal aggregation of the resource (Australian Marine Community Profile extension to ISO19115/19139)</description></item><item><name>mcp:EX_TemporalExtent</name><displayName>Temporal Extent (MCP)</displayName><description>time period covered by the content of the dataset</description></item><item><name>mcp:beginTime</name><displayName>Begin Time</displayName><description>start of time period covered by the dataset (deprecated - use gml: elements in the extent element instead)</description></item><item><name>mcp:endTime</name><displayName>End Time</displayName><description>end of time period covered by the dataset (deprecated - use gml: elements in the extent element instead)</description></item><item><name>mcp:MD_CreativeCommons</name><displayName>Creative Commons</displayName><description>Creative Commons Constraints can be chosen in this element</description></item><item><name>mcp:dataParameters</name><displayName>Data Parameters</displayName><description>Describes the Parameters or variables included in dataset</description></item><item><name>mcp:dataParameter</name><displayName>Data Parameter Info</displayName><description>Details about a specific Parameter, including he various names and labels used for that parameter; the unit-of-measurement (UOM) used; the minimum and maximum values measured in the dataset, and a description of the parameter the definitions of the parameters information</description></item><item><name>mcp:parameterName</name><displayName>Parameter Name</displayName><description>Specific Parameter's name or label.  Details include whether this is a shortname, longname, code or "other".  It also the details of a vocabulary list (if one is known) that the label or name belongs to, and the label's definition</description></item><item><name>mcp:name</name><displayName>Name</displayName><description>Name of Parameter or Unit of Measurement (UOM) depending on parent</description></item><item><name>mcp:type</name><displayName>Type</displayName><description>Type of Name - typically: long, short, code or other</description></item><item><name>mcp:usedInDataset</name><displayName>Used in dataset?</displayName><description>Specific Parameter or UOM name being discussed in this element</description></item><item><name>mcp:vocabularyListURL</name><displayName>Names VocabularyList URL</displayName><description>Version of the parameter vocabulary list that includes and defines this name;   Only use this, if the name actually is defined in a parameter or "UOM" vocabulary list that is available from the web</description></item><item><name>mcp:vocabularyListVersion</name><displayName>Names VocabularyList Version</displayName><description>Version of the parameter vocabulary list that includes and defines this name;</description></item><item><name>mcp:vocabularyListAuthority</name><displayName>Names VocabularyList Authority</displayName><description>Authority usually means a body or organisation regulating a vocabulary list.  Use this field if the shortname or longname or param-code are defined in a parameter or "UOM" vocabulary list that is defined, maintained or regulated by a particular body or organisation</description></item><item><name>mcp:parameterMinimumValue</name><displayName>Min.Value in dataset</displayName><description>Minimum value measured - for this parameter, within this dataset</description></item><item><name>mcp:parameterMaximumValue</name><displayName>Max.Value in dataset</displayName><description>Maximum value measured - for this parameter, within this dataset</description></item><item><name>mcp:parameterDescription</name><displayName>Parameter Description</displayName><description>Description of Param</description></item><item><name>mcp:localDefinition</name><displayName>Local definition</displayName><description>Local definition of Param or UOM; Used where an external vocabulary hasn't been used, or where an external vocab's definition is insufficient</description></item><item><name>mcp:parameterUnits</name><displayName>Parameter unit of measurement</displayName><description>Includes names and labels for the UOM, as well as details of vocabulary Lists that include the label, and defnitions.
             This can be a standard UOM such as SI units; or might be a relative/local measurement. An example of the latter is:

	PARAM name: field-based surface turbidity measure;
	PARAM defn:   visibility test taken at 1,3 aand 5 feet below surface;
	PARAM UOM:   possible value range is 10-0, 0 means clear;

Test involves visible detection of an item at 1, 3, and 5 feet, under the water surface.  The item placed under the water is a plate inscribed with a shape enclosing 4 dots; and that shape is of varying sizes.
    </description></item><item><name>mcp:MD_DataCommons</name><displayName>Data Commons</displayName><description>Data Commons Constraints can be chosen in this element</description></item><item><name>mcp:attributionConstraints</name><displayName>Attribution Constraints</displayName><description>
Describes how and when the resource should be attributed as well as who the
resource should be attributed to. For example: Jones, C, 3D Mining Data, 
International Journal of Mining, University Press, must be cited whenever this
data is referred to in a paper.
    </description></item><item><name>mcp:derivativeConstraints</name><displayName>Derivative Constraints</displayName><description>
Describes the constraints on products that may be derived from this resource.
    </description></item><item><name>mcp:commercialUseConstraints</name><displayName>Commercial Use Constraints</displayName><description>
Describes what the constraints are if you want to make use of this resource commercially.  
    </description></item><item><name>mcp:collectiveWorksConstraints</name><displayName>Collective Work Constraints </displayName><description>
Describes what the constraints are if you wish to include this resource in a collective work.
    </description></item><item><name>mcp:otherConstraints</name><displayName>Other Constraints </displayName><description>
Describes any constraints on using this resource that are not captured by the other constraint fields.
    </description></item></display_items>